http://www.ucc.ca/privacy-statement/

National Internment Centenary Committee
National Ukrainian Education Council (NUEC)
HomePrivacy StatementPrivacy Statement
The Ukrainian Canadian Congress National is committed to protecting your personal information.  This is our privacy commitment to you as a donor, volunteer and a friend of the UCC.
We collect your personal information only to provide services for which you have registered, to understand your needs and to assist us in creating new services that will serve you better.
We do not disclose your personal information to any other organization or individual outside the UCC National unless it is necessary to provide you with services from the UCC or when required by law.
Your personal information is processed and stored in secure and confidential databases with strict access controls.
If you have questions or concerns about how your personal information is gathered, used or retained, or wish to opt out of receiving specific UCC communications, please email us at ucc@ucc.ca
Contact Us
Head Office - Winnipeg
Address: 203-952 Main Street, Winnipeg, Manitoba R2W 3P4
Toll-Free Telephone: 1-866-942-4627
Email: ucc@ucc.ca
UCC National Office – Ottawa
Address: 130 Albert Street, Suite 500, Ottawa, Ontario K1P 1B1
Telephone: (613) 232-8822; Fax: (613) 238-3822
Latest News
Resolutions adopted by the XXVI Triennial Congress of Ukrainian Canadians
November 18, 2019 in News
To protect human rights, target those who abuse them
December 10, 2020 in News
Ukrainian Christmas Shopping 2020
December 9, 2020 in Community News
UCC welcomes additional Canadian support for women and most vulnerable in Ukraine
December 9, 2020 in News
UCC AffiliationsUkrainian Canadian Foundation of Taras Shevchenko
Canada-Ukraine Foundation
Canadian Ethnocultural Council
Ukrainian World Congress
Join Our Email List
Subscribe
Copyright © 2020 All Rights Reserved by Ukrainian Canadian Congress National. Charity BN/Registration of UCCC Trust # 11927346 RR0001. Privacy Statement
div#stuning-header .dfd-stuning-header-bg-container {background-image: url(https://www.ucc.ca/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Parliamentary_Internship_Program_1920x400.jpg);background-size: cover;background-position: center center;background-attachment: scroll;background-repeat: no-repeat;}#stuning-header div.page-title-inner {min-height: 400px;}
Subscribe to our email list
Subscribe
Be the first one to receive our exclusive news, event invitations and engagement opportunities
